Free Shipping on Orders $60+ (Exclusions Apply)

* [image/svg+xml](javascript:void(0))
* [image/svg+xml](javascript:void(0))
* [image/svg+xml](javascript:void(0))

### Start typing and hit Enter

  image/svg+xml

[](javascript:void(0))

[](javascript:void(0))

### Shopping Cart

0

Your shopping bag is empty

[](javascript:void(0))

image/svg+xml [image/svg+xml 0](javascript:void(0))

[Pumping](javascript:void(0) "Pumping")

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------------------------

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

[Juvenile Travel & Home Safety](javascript:void(0) "Juvenile Travel & Home Safety")

----------------------------------------------------

----------------------------------------------------

------------------------------------------------------------------

--------------------------------------------------------------

------------------------------------------------------------

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

--------------------------------------------------------

[Support](javascript:void(0) "Support")

------------------------------------------------------------------------

--------------------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

----------------------------------------------------------------------------

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------

Log In

or

[Register now](javascript:void(0))

Reset your password
-------------------

Cancel

Register

register

or

[Back to login](javascript:void(0))

Close

Great to have you back!
-----------------------

Log In

Don’t have an account?[Register now](javascript:void(0))

Reset your password
-------------------

Cancel

Register

register

[Back to login](javascript:void(0))

[](javascript:void(0))

Privacy policy
==============

Evenflo Feeding respects your privacy and understands that it is important to you. Likewise, your privacy is important to us and, as such, we will strive to keep your personal information confidential and avoid unwanted solicitations. This Privacy Statement describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from evenflofeeding.com and subdomains of evenflofeeding.com (the “Site”).

**Collecting Personal Information  
**When you visit the Site, we collect certain information about your device, your interaction with the Site, and information necessary to process your purchases. We may also collect additional information if you contact us for customer support. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to any information that can uniquely identify an individual (including the information below) as “Personal Information”. See the list below for more information about what Personal Information we collect and why.

Device information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:** version of web browser, IP address, time zone, cookie information, what sites or products you view, search terms, and how you interact with the Site.
* **Purpose of collection:** to load the Site accurately for you, and to perform analytics on Site usage to optimize our Site.
* **Source of collection:** Collected automatically when you access our Site using cookies, log files, web beacons, tags, or pixels.

* **Disclosure for a business purpose:**shared with our order processor (Shopify), payment gateways, fulfillment centers, analytics vendors, behavioral advertising partners, subsidiaries, and/or companies we share trademark licenses with to provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

Order information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:**name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number), items added to or removed from cart, customer click ID, customer agent ID, and checkout progress

* **Purpose of collection:** to provide products or services to you to fulfill our contract, to process your payment information, arrange for shipping, and provide you with invoices and/or order confirmations, communicate with you, screen our orders for potential risk or fraud, and when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
* **Source of collection:** collected from you.

* **Disclosure for a business purpose:**shared with our order processor (Shopify), payment gateways, fulfillment centers, analytics vendors, behavioral advertising partners, subsidiaries, and/or companies we share trademark licenses with to provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

Customer support information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:** _name, email address, phone number, inquiry message_
* **Purpose of collection:** to provide customer support.
* **Source of collection:** collected from you.
* **Disclosure for a business purpose:** shared with consumer services team, and/or an International Board-Certified Lactation Consultant for product and breast or bottle feeding support.

**Minors  
**The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of _13_. We do not intentionally collect Personal Information from children. If you are the parent or guardian and believe your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at the address below to request deletion.

**Sharing Personal Information  
**We share your Personal Information with service providers to help us provide our services and fulfill our contracts with you, as described above. For example:

* We use Shopify to power our online store. You can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: [https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).
* We may share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

**Behavioral Advertising  
**As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For example:

* We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

* We share information about your use of the Site, your purchases, and your interaction with our ads on other websites with our advertising partners. We collect and share some of this information directly with our advertising partners, and in some cases through the use of cookies or other similar technologies (which you may consent to, depending on your location).

For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work).

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

* _FACEBOOK -_ [_https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads_](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads)
* _GOOGLE -_ [_https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous_](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous)
* _BING -_ [_https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads_](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)_\]_

_Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:_  [_http://optout.aboutads.info/_](http://optout.aboutads.info/)_._

**_Using Personal Information  
_**_We use your personal Information to provide our services to you, which includes: offering products for sale, processing payments, shipping and fulfillment of your order, and keeping you up to date on new products, services, and offers._

**_Retention  
_**_When you place an order through the Site, we will retain your Personal Information for our records unless and until you ask us to erase this information. For more information on your right of erasure, please see the ‘Your rights’ section below._

**_CCPA  
_**_If you are a resident of California, you have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you (also known as the ‘Right to Know’), to port it to a new service, and to ask that your Personal Information be corrected, updated, or erased. If you would like to exercise these rights, please contact us through the contact information below \[OR INSERT ALTERNATIVE INSTRUCTIONS FOR SENDING ACCESS, ERASURE, CORRECTION, AND PORTABILITY REQUESTS\]._

_If you would like to designate an authorized agent to submit these requests on your behalf, please contact us at the address below._

**_Cookies  
_**_A cookie is a small amount of information that’s downloaded to your computer or device when you visit our Site. We use a number of different cookies, including functional, performance, advertising, and social media or content cookies. Cookies make your browsing experience better by allowing the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login and region selection). This means you don’t have to re-enter this information each time you return to the site or browse from one page to another. Cookies also provide information on how people use the website, for instance whether it’s their first time visiting or if they are a frequent visitor._

_We use the following cookies to optimize your experience on our Site and to provide our services._

**_Cookies Necessary for the Functioning of the Store_**

| **Name** | **Function** |
| --- | --- |
| _\_ab_ | Used in connection with access to admin. |
| _\_secure\_session\_id_ | Used in connection with navigation through a storefront. |
| _cart_ | Used in connection with shopping cart. |
| _cart\_sig_ | Used in connection with checkout. |
| _cart\_ts_ | Used in connection with checkout. |
| _checkout\_token_ | Used in connection with checkout. |
| _secret_ | Used in connection with checkout. |
| _secure\_customer\_sig_ | Used in connection with customer login. |
| _storefront\_digest_ | Used in connection with customer login. |
| _\_shopify\_u_ | Used to facilitate updating customer account information. |

**_Reporting and Analytics_**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Name** | **Function** |
| _\_tracking\_consent_ | Tracking preferences. |
| _\_landing\_page_ | Track landing pages |
| _\_orig\_referrer_ | Track landing pages |
| _\_s_ | Shopify analytics. |
| _\_shopify\_fs_ | Shopify analytics. |
| _\_shopify\_s_ | Shopify analytics. |
| _\_shopify\_sa\_p_ | Shopify analytics relating to marketing & referrals. |
| _\_shopify\_sa\_t_ | Shopify analytics relating to marketing & referrals. |
| _\_shopify\_y_ | Shopify analytics. |
| _\_y_ | Shopify analytics. |

_The length of time that a cookie remains on your computer or mobile device depends on whether it is a “persistent” or “session” cookie. Session cookies last until you stop browsing and persistent cookies last until they expire or are deleted. Most of the cookies we use are persistent and will expire between 30 minutes and two years from the date they are downloaded to your device._

_You can control and manage cookies in various ways. Please keep in mind that removing or blocking cookies can negatively impact your user experience and parts of our website may no longer be fully accessible._

_Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can choose whether or not to accept cookies through your browser controls, often found in your browser’s “Tools” or “Preferences” menu. For more information on how to modify your browser settings or how to block, manage or filter cookies can be found in your browser’s help file or through such sites as_ _www.allaboutcookies.org__._

_Additionally, please note that blocking cookies may not completely prevent how we share information with third parties such as our advertising partners. To exercise your rights or opt-out of certain uses of your information by these parties, please follow the instructions in the “Behavioural Advertising” section above._

**_Do Not Track  
_**_Please note that because there is no consistent industry understanding of how to respond to “Do Not Track” signals, we do not alter our data collection and usage practices when we detect such a signal from your browser._

**_Linked Sites  
_**This website does contain links to third-party websites. While we do not share your personal information with these third parties, you should be aware that Evenflo Feeding maintains no control over these entities and is not responsible for their privacy practices. Accordingly, we encourage you to learn more about the privacy policies of these companies.

**_Changes  
_**_We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons._

**_Contact  
_**_For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by mail using the details provided below:_

_Evenflo Feeding, Inc., 9277 Centre Pointe Drive, Suite 160, West Chester OH 45069, United States_

_Phone: 1-866-334-BABY_

_Email:_ [_support@evenflofeeding.com_](mailto:support@evenflofeeding.com)

_Last updated: August 30, 2021_

#### Shop

#### Company

#### Resources

#### Support

* [1-855-334-BABY (2229)](tel:(855)334-2229 "Phone: 1-855-334-BABY (2229)")

#### Evenflo Feeding • Since 1920

SUBSCRIBE

-

Add to Cart

[](javascript:void(0))

[](javascript:void(0))

Added to cart successfully!

Price :

QTY :

CART TOTALS :

There are items  
in your cart

CART TOTALS :

Continue shopping Go to cart Proceed to checkout

#### [Balance + Bottles - WIDE Neck, Plastic](https://www.evenflofeeding.com/products/balance-baby-bottles-wide-plastic)

$12.99

#### [Balance + Bottles - GLASS, WIDE Neck](https://www.evenflofeeding.com/products/balance-bottles-glass-wide-neck)

$29.99

#### [Balance + Bottles - STANDARD Neck, Plastic](https://www.evenflofeeding.com/products/balance-bottles-standard-neck-plastic)

$14.99

#### [Balance + Bottles - Angled, Woodland Creatures, STANDARD Neck, Plastic](https://www.evenflofeeding.com/products/balance-baby-bottles-copy)

$29.99

[_image/svg+xml_ 0](javascript:void(0))
